<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Eli's Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.elinelsonmarsden.xyz/</link>
    <description>Stuff i say.</description>
    <item>
      <title>Me</title>
      <link>/Blogs/Who-am-i.html</link>
      <description><p>My name is Eli Nelson-Marsden. I live on the wester side of Australia and I am 16 as of writing and am
                currently in my final year of high school. I'm writing this as I am someone who is very hard to find and
                get in connact with. I want to explain my reasonings for my lack of online presents.</p>
            <p>late twenty twenty one and early twenty twenty two, i finally deicided to delete all of my social media
                as i was disappointed with what i was using it for and how i felt like i was wasting my time. This is
                probably the second best decision i have ever made in my life. I have become more productive and ive
                felt happier in general i have also began working out, wheather that is the reason im happier or just a
                bi-product is up to you but if i never quit social media i wouldnt be doing it.</p>
            <p>I have a love hate realtionship with politics. I find political discussion exstremly intresting, yet
                they nearly always fall into a mob mentally on stupidity and internet buzzwords. This occurs because
                Social media sites especially twitter encourages political content. Politics people angry and riled up
                thus keeping you on the site arguing, wasting time and not really achieving anything as after an
                argument people. "educational" videos i find the most egregious in the instance of wasting time,
                servered
                to you to make you think that your using your time to learn, when you just sitting there like a monkey
                watching a 30 second video of information that will have no relevance to you in future. (Spending your
                time lying on your bed just stairing at the ceiling would be a better use of you time.)
                I on occasion have done similar actions, but I try to keep to a minimum and hopfully not
                at all as i find it to be in my own arbitrary opinion to be stupid.</p>
            <p>Social media makes you stupid and boring. Sites like facebook, twitter and instagram run on skinner box
                systems to make your dopamine respetors in your brain and essentially turn your brain to mush. When you
                feeling even the slights bit bored your first response is to grab your phone yet once you grab it you
                instantlly want to throw the damn thing away because you inherinty know that you shouldn't be doing it.
                This is cognitive dissonance.</p>
            <p>TL;DR: Social media, Phone, Bad. It pretty sad.
            </p>

            <p>By Eli<a href="mailto:eli@nelsonmarsden.com">(Reply too)</a></p></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>